[{"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh hi, my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, I'm serious, my friend. I went to medical school, but I still have to pass my licensing exam", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I've taken it. Three times. I almost passed the last one", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, you're basically a doctor. Right? I mean, people do call you doctor", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Well, can I introduce you as doctor", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "It was a mi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Now why would a junior high school want to screw with my head", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh hi, my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "It's Sue my friend, this old braless friend I hate.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh hi, my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Like what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Right. Elevate your legs", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How am I gonna fill two hours", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "And give you the chance to see some real disappointed kids.", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh no", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No way, my friend. You've brought nothing but a mountain of misfortune and humiliation. Now get out", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What for? Oh come on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I think it has something to do with me", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Where have you been? You know, you're on next", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Got lost? We went to school here for three years", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh my God. You had sex. You had sex with my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "The Portuguese waitress", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It was a great lunch, my friend. Thanks", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Mrs. my friend, from the tobacco company called me. We had a little po", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "those things, deadly dangerous. A long time ago my uncle and a date are driving, like, through that place. They see one on the road, drags him out of the road, and chews his face off. Listen, we'll call you if anything opens up. Okay, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Abstinence.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Right. my friend", "qsentId": 28}]